export default data = [
  {
      question: "Ms.Liu usually gives us a lot of homework, ______ she didn’t give us any today",
      options: ["but","if","or","so"],
      correct_option: "but"
  },
  {
      question: "Playing games on the cellphone ______ popular with high school students",
      options: ["is","are","being","to be"],
      correct_option: "is	"
  },
  {
      question: "There ______ more than twenty clubs in our school. Which one would you like to join?",
      options: ["has","have","is","are"],
      correct_option: "are"
  },
  {
      question: "Diane had a bad cold last week. She is still too ______ to go mountain climbing with you",
      options: ["busy","short","weak","young"],
      correct_option: "weak"
  },
  {
      question: "The book under Mary’s desk is ______, but I don’t know why it is there",
      options: ["us","me","my","mine"],
      correct_option: "mine"
  },
  {
      question: "Last night a garbage truck hit a tree and turned over. Now the street is ______ with lots of garbage",
      options: ["dark","dirty","heavy","poor"],
      correct_option: "dirty	"
  },
  {
      question: "It almost killed Kevin to take care of his baby sister for one afternoon. He wondered how his mom could do ______ every day",
      options: ["her","it","one","them"],
      correct_option: "it	"
  },
  {
      question: "Joyce tells her brother everything. She never ______ anything from him",
      options: ["covers","believes","hides","takes"],
      correct_option: "hides"
  },
  {
      question: "Ben always uses his birthday as a(n) ______ to ask Dad to buy him something expensive",
      options: ["action","excuse","prize","rule"],
      correct_option: "excuse"
  },
  {
      question: "	______ that last piece of pie? If not, can I have it? I didn’t eat much this morning",
      options: ["Had you eaten","Were you eating","Do you eat","Are you going to eat"],
      correct_option: "Are you going to eat"
  },
  {
      question: "Everyone in the class enjoys playing chess ______ Bill; he thinks the game is boring",
      options: ["except","for","like","of"],
      correct_option: "except	"
  },
  {
      question: "In my school days, I ______ to English radio programs every day. That was how I learned English at that time",
      options: ["listen","have listened","used to listen","was listening"],
      correct_option: "used to listen"
  },
  {
      question: "Tom’s voice ______ when he talks about his neighbors. He speaks faster, his face becomes redder and you can almost see fire in his eyes",
      options: ["appears","drops","grows","rises"],
      correct_option: "rises"
  },
  {
      question: "______ other waiters in the restaurant have worked here longer than Clark; only Lois and Lana started working here before him",
      options: ["All","Most","Some","Few"],
      correct_option: "Few"
  },
]
